Guide to the Peter Reddaway Samizdat collection, 1950-2010 GRC0002
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Mainstream, Circa 1960s to 1990s; Series 4
  - Individual, Series 4 Subseries 4
    - [Oganian, Rafael'], 1982 July 2; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 39, Folder 16)
    - [Ogorodnikov, Aleksandr], 1976 August 5-1978 November 28; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 39, Folder 17)
    - [Alexander] Ogoronikov "Christian Seminar", 1976-1989; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 39, Folder 18)
    - [Ogurtsov, Igor'], 1977 March 22-1992 December 10; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 39, Folder 19)
    - [Okudzhava, Bulat], 1987 July 5; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 39, Folder 20)
    - [Okuneva, Ruth], 1981 March 19; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 39, Folder 21)
    - [Olekhnovich, Vera], 1975; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 39, Folder 22)
    - [Olitskaia, Ekaterina], 1976 June; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 39, Folder 23)
    - [Ordynskii, Vadim], 1987 June; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 39, Folder 24)
    - [Orekhov, Viktor], 1991 February 13; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 39, Folder 25)
    - Orlov, Yury [1/2], 1973-1986; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 39, Folder 26)
    - Orlov, Yury [2/2], 1977-1978; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 39, Folder 27)
    - Yu[ry] Orlov [1/2], 1978-1987; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 39, Folder 28)
    - Yu[ry] Orlov [2/2], 1978; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 39, Folder 29)
    - [Orlovskii, Ernst], 1959 March 14-1987 April; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 40, Folder 1)
    - [Osadchii, Mikhailo], 1977 April 15-1981 June 7; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 40, Folder 2)
    - [Osipov, Vladimir], 1977 February 14; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 40, Folder 3)
    - Osipov [Vladimir] + "Veche" [1/4], 1977-1988; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 40, Folder 4)
    - Osipov [Vladimir] + "Veche" [2/4], 1973-1977; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 40, Folder 5)
    - Osipov [Vladimir] + "Veche" [3/4], 1971-1975; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 40, Folder 6)
    - Osipov [Vladimir] + "Veche" [4/4], 1971-1972; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 40, Folder 7)
    - [Osipova, A.], 1971 November 1; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 40, Folder 8)
    - [Osipova, Tat'iana], 1981 April 13-1989 May 29; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 40, Folder 9)
    - [Osmanov, Iurii], 1987 January 10; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 40, Folder 10)
    - [Ostin, Entoni], 1981 November 25; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 40, Folder 11)
    - [Ostrovskaia, Natal'ia], 1979 July 27; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 40, Folder 12)
    - [Ostrovskii, Vladimir], 1978 September; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 40, Folder 13)
    - [Ovanes, David], 1982 August 20; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 40, Folder 14)
    - [Ovsienko, Vasil'], 1977 August 4-1980; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 40, Folder 15)
    - [Ozernoi, Leonid], 1985 February 24; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 40, Folder 16)
    - [Ozhegov, Rail], 1979 June 25-1983 February 27; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 40, Folder 17)
    - [Pachagin, Vladimir], 1979 March 7; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 40, Folder 18)
    - [Pailodze, Valentina], 1975 September 27; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 40, Folder 19)
    - [Pakh, Tibor], 1981 November 6; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 40, Folder 20)
    - [Pal'chikov, Aleksandr], undated; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 40, Folder 21)
    - [Pankov, Nikolai], 1984 March 12-1985 March 27; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 40, Folder 22)
    - [Panov, Valerii], 1973 August 15-1976 August 17; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 40, Folder 23)
    - [Papernyi, Zinovii], 1970 September 9; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 40, Folder 24)
    - A[vtandil] Papiashvili [1/2], 1977-1980; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 40, Folder 25)
    - A[vtandil] Papiashvili [2/2], 1977 March 18-1978 March 26; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 40, Folder 26)
    - [Paradzhanov, Sergei], 1976 May 11-1984 May 17; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 40, Folder 27)
    - [Parasenkov, Fiodor], 1983 January 24; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 40, Folder 28)
    - [Paritskii, Aleksandr], 1981 November 16-1982 October 25; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 41, Folder 1)
    - [Pashnin, Evgenii], 1979-1984 April 22; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 41, Folder 2)
    - [Patsiukevich, V.G.], 1981 November 13; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 41, Folder 3)
    - [Pavlenkov, Vladlen], 1972 December 3; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 41, Folder 4)
    - [Pavlov, Leonid], 1976 December 5-1977 February 18; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 41, Folder 5)
    - [Pavlov, Nikolai], 1981 September 22- 1987 July 5; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 41, Folder 6)
    - [Pavlov, Vladimir], 1976 November 29; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 41, Folder 7)
    - [Pavlovich, Antoniuk], 1980 January; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 41, Folder 8)
    - [Pavlovskii, Gleb], undated; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 41, Folder 9)
    - [Pechkin, M.], 1974 September 29; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 41, Folder 10)
    - [Penson, Boris], 1975 July 2-1975 October 30; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 41, Folder 11)
    - [Penzin, Andrei], 1978 May; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 41, Folder 12)
    - [Perchatkin, Boris], 1979 June 30-1979 July 1; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 41, Folder 13)
    - [Peretykin, Elup], 1977 March 19; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 41, Folder 14)
    - [Pergamanik, Efim], 1977 November; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 41, Folder 15)
    - [Petkus, Viktoras], 1978 July 18-1984 May 31; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 41, Folder 16)
    - [Petrash, Stefaniia], 1980 November 10-1983 May 10; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 41, Folder 17)
    - [Petrenko, Mariia], 1980 November 12-1981 January 3; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 41, Folder 18)
    - [Petrov, Viacheslav], 1989 January-1990 November 25; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 41, Folder 19)
    - [Petrov-Agatov, Aleksandr], 1965 July 19-1978 December 6; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 41, Folder 20)
    - [Petrovskii, L.], 1969 August 20; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 41, Folder 21)
    - [Petrunovskii, Anatolii], 1987 December; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 41, Folder 22)
    - [Pevzner, Evgenii], 1975 May 16; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 41, Folder 23)
    - [Pianov, Oleg], 1985 January 21-1985 March 9; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 41, Folder 24)
    - [Piatkys, Viktoras], 1978 July 16-1983; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 41, Folder 25)
    - [Pidgorodetsky, Vasil'], 1976 March-1979 January; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 41, Folder 26)
    - [Pidgorodnii, Vasil'], 1979 March 1; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 41, Folder 27)
    - Pimenov [Revol't], 1968-1975; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 41, Folder 28)
    - [Pin, Khy], 1980; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 41, Folder 29)
    - [Pinkhasov], 1974 January 22; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 41, Folder 30)
    - [Pinkskii, Leonid], 1981 March 30; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 41, Folder 31)
    - [Pinsker, Boris], 1989 March 1-1989 March 17; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 41, Folder 32)
    - [Pinsker, Mark], 1978 December 8; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 41, Folder 33)
    - [Pisarev, Sergei], 1970 April 7-1971 July 8; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 41, Folder 34)
    - [Pishchenko, Anatolii], 1979 August; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 41, Folder 35)
    - [Pisigin, Valerii], 1989 July 5; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 41, Folder 36)
    - [Plakhotniuk, Nikolai], 1977 January 4-1982; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 41, Folder 37)
    - [Pleshakov, Aleksievich], 1981 July 24; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 41, Folder 38)
    - [Pletschko, Frieda], 1979 March 27; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 41, Folder 39)
    - [Plumna, Piatrac], 1977 June 6-1977 August 3; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 41, Folder 40)
    - [Plyushch, Leonid], 1979 August 7; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 41, Folder 41)
    - Plyushch [Leonid] [1/4], 1975-1978; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 41, Folder 42)
    - Plyushch [Leonid] [2/4], 1969-1975; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 41, Folder 43)
    - Plyushch [Leonid] [3/4], 1972-1976; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 42, Folder 1)
    - Plyushch [Leonid] [4/4], 1972-1976; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 42, Folder 2)
    - [Podgoretskii, Vasil'], undated; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 42, Folder 3)
    - [Pod''iachaia, Dina], undated; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 42, Folder 4)
    - [Pod''iapol'skii, Grigorii], 1973 April 9-1976 March 9; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 42, Folder 5)
    - [Podrabinek, Kirill], 1977 July 24-1981 January 12; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 42, Folder 6)
    - Podrabineks [Kirill + Aleksander], 1978-1998; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 42, Folder 7)
    - Podrabineks [Kirill + Aleksander], 1977-1990; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 42, Folder 8)
    - Aleksander Podrabnik Karatel'naia Meditsina g. [1/2], 1977; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 42, Folder 9)
    - Aleksander Podrabnik Karatel'naia Meditsina g. [2/2], 1977; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 42, Folder 10)
    - [Pogiby, Nikolai], 1980 November 4; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 42, Folder 11)
    - [Pogorilyi, Valentin], 1987 April 29; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 42, Folder 12)
    - [Pohyba, Mykola], 1982 July 13; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 43, Folder 1)
    - [Poliakov, G.], 1975; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 43, Folder 2)
    - [Poliakov, Igor'], 1979 October 8; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 43, Folder 3)
    - [Polianskii, Nikolai], 1981 November 5; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 43, Folder 4)
    - [Polikanov, Sergei], 1978 October 10-1979 May 11; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 43, Folder 5)
    - [Arkhimandrit Polikarp], 1986 November; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 43, Folder 6)
    - [Polishchuk, Arkadii], 1977 July 31; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 43, Folder 7)
    - [Polovchak, Vladimir], 1981 February 12; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 43, Folder 8)
    - [Poltinnikov, Isaak], 1979 July 23; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 43, Folder 9)
    - Poltorak [Vadim, Inoi Mad'iar, Liningrad], 1977; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 43, Folder 10)
    - [Pomazov, Vitalii], 1982 April 21; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 43, Folder 11)
    - [Pomerants, Grigorii], 1967-1976 September 15; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 43, Folder 12)
    - [Pomerantsev, Igor'], 1978 October 23; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 43, Folder 13)
    - [Pomniashchii, Ivan], 1986 February 14; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 43, Folder 14)
    - [Pomozov, Vitalii], 1978 July 10; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 43, Folder 15)
    - [Ponomarev], 1980 November 19; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 43, Folder 16)
    - [Ponomarev, Anatolii], 1979 March 27-1979 July 11; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 43, Folder 17)
    - [Ponomarev, Lev], 1990 January; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 43, Folder 18)
    - [Ponomarev, Valerii], 1980 April 29; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 43, Folder 19)
    - [Popov, Aleksandr], 1986 April 25; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 43, Folder 20)
    - [Popov, Evgenii], 1980 December 18; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 43, Folder 21)
    - [Popov, Kirill], 1985 September 3-1986 June 18; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 43, Folder 22)
    - [Popov, Nikolai], 1979 March 22; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 43, Folder 23)
    - [Popov, Oleg], 1981 September 22-1982 January 5; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 43, Folder 24)
    - [Popova, Roza], 1980 October 30; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 43, Folder 25)
    - [Popovskii, Mark], 1978 January 19-1978 March 4; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 43, Folder 26)
    - [Popovych, Oksana], 1976 May 3; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 43, Folder 27)
    - [Poresh, Vladimir], 1979 March 2-1984 October 23; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 43, Folder 28)
    - [Potapenko, Vitalii], 1968 October24; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 43, Folder 29)
    - [Potutkin, Sergei], 1984 May 4-1987 January 29; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 43, Folder 30)
    - [Pozdniakov, Anatolii], 1979 November 15; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 43, Folder 31)
    - [Pranskunaite, Ona], 1979 September; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 43, Folder 32)
    - [Pribytkov, Lev], 1980 February 17; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 43, Folder 33)
    - [Prigoniker, Elizaveta], 1967 September-1973 January 22; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 43, Folder 34)
    - [Prikhod'ko, Grigorii], 1975 November 17; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 43, Folder 35)
    - [Proniuk, Evghen], 1977 March 26-1977 December 8; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 43, Folder 36)
    - [Protsenko, Pavel], 1986 November 4-1986 December 26; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 43, Folder 37)
    - [Prusakov, Valentin], 1968 March; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 43, Folder 38)
    - [Pshenitsyn, Mikhail], 1977 December 19; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 43, Folder 39)
    - [Purtov, Sergei], undated; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 43, Folder 40)
    - [Rabin, Oskar], 1978 July 7; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 43, Folder 41)
    - [Radzinskii, Oleg], 1983 March 30-1983 December27; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 43, Folder 42)
    - [Rafal'skii, Viktor], 1976 March 1-1987 June 17; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 43, Folder 43)
    - [Raffe, Arthur], 1981 June 5; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 43, Folder 44)
    - [Ragaishis, Romal'das], 1979 July 9-1979 July 10; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 43, Folder 45)
    - [Raikov, Aleksandr], 1979 February 1; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 43, Folder 46)
    - [Raksha, Petr], 1978; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 43, Folder 47)
    - [Rasputin, Valentin], 1982 January 13; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 43, Folder 48)
    - [Rassokha, Igor'], 1989 September; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 43, Folder 49)
    - [Ratushinkaia, Irina], 1982 September 17-1987 February 20; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 44, Folder 1)
    - [Raush Family], 1981 June-1981 August 12; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 44, Folder 2)
    - [Ravin'sh, Maigonis], 1984; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 44, Folder 3)
    - [Razymnyi, Sergei], 1969-1971 March 24; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 44, Folder 4)
    - [Rebrik, Bogdan], 1976 February-1977 December; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 44, Folder 5)
    - [Redin, Anatolii], 1979 March 22; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 44, Folder 6)
    - [Regel'son, Lev], 1976 January 6-1980 September 25; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 44, Folder 7)
    - [Reinis, Peteris], undated; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 44, Folder 8)
    - [Reitman, Mark], 1982 June-1985 February 8; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 44, Folder 9)
    - [Rendel', Leonid], 1968 February 20-1991 March 25; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 44, Folder 10)
    - [Repin, Valerii], 1983 March 7-1983 May 24; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 44, Folder 11)
    - [Repnikov, Viacheslav], 1976 October 3-1976 October 27; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 44, Folder 12)
    - [Reshetovskaia, N.], 1980 April 9; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 44, Folder 13)
    - [Resov, Aleksandr], 1967; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 44, Folder 14)
    - [Reznichenko, Petr], 1983 October; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 44, Folder 15)
    - [Reznikov, Vasilii], 1972; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 44, Folder 16)
    - [Rianzhin, Aleksandr], 1986 August 24; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 44, Folder 17)
    - [Riga, Aleksandr], 1985 August 20; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 44, Folder 18)
    - [Rips, Il'ia], 1972 August 7; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 44, Folder 19)
    - [Riskhiladze, Viktor], 1977 April 13; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 44, Folder 20)
    - [Rivkin, Mikhail], 1983 October 18-1984 January 11; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 44, Folder 21)
    - [Rode, Gunars], 1976 June 19-1977 September 14; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 44, Folder 22)
    - [Rodionova-Ignatova, Elena], 1980 August 25; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 44, Folder 23)
    - [Roginskii, Arsenii], 1979 November 28-1982 December 9; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 44, Folder 24)
    - [Roitkov-Fodoriachik, Dina], 1974 June 10; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 44, Folder 25)
    - [Rokusuev, Andrei], 1985 August 20; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 44, Folder 26)
    - [Romanenko, Vitalii], 1988 July 17; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 44, Folder 27)
    - [Romanov, Aleksandr], 1991 January 7; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 44, Folder 28)
    - V[asiliy] Romanyuk, 1972 December 31-1976; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 44, Folder 29)
    - Romanyuk, [Vasily], 1976 December-1995 July 16; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 44, Folder 30)
    - [Romashov, Boris], 1982 December 28-1983 January 5; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 44, Folder 31)
    - [Ronovskaia, Anna], 1978; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 44, Folder 32)
    - [Rose, Endel], 1982 April 25; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 44, Folder 33)
    - [Rossoshanskii, K.A.], 1985 November 11; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 44, Folder 34)
    - [Rostropovich, Mstislav], 1970 October 31-1978 March 27; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 44, Folder 35)
    - [Rostropovich, Veronika], 1981 April 9; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 44, Folder 36)
    - [Rozenman, Alla], 1973 April 23; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 44, Folder 37)
    - [Rozenshtein, Grigorii], 1977 March 16; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 44, Folder 38)
    - [Rozentsveig, Iu.], 1979 February 21; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 44, Folder 39)
    - [Rozhdestvov, Vladimir], 1977 October-1985 March 30; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 44, Folder 40)
    - [Rozhkalns, Gunta], 1983 January 20-1986 June 12; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 44, Folder 41)
    - [Ruban, Petr], 1977 January 14-1985 November 28; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 44, Folder 42)
    - [Rubin, Vitalii], 1974 February 1-1981 April 1; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 44, Folder 43)
    - [Rubtsov, Vladimir], 1977 January 18; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 44, Folder 44)
    - [Rudenko, Raisa Mikola], 1975 September 15-1981 November 5; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 44, Folder 45)
    - [Rulev-Kagan, Lazar'], 1985 September 13; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 45, Folder 1)
    - [Ruminskaia, Marina], 1984 September 24-1984 October 4; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 45, Folder 2)
    - [Rusak, Vladimir], 1988 June 24; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 45, Folder 3)
    - [Rusin, Konstantin], 1976 September 11; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 45, Folder 4)
    - [Rustamov, Aslan], 1979 March 29; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 45, Folder 5)
    - [Ruzina, Tat'iana], 1984 August 9-1985 February; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 45, Folder 6)
    - [Rybakov, Iulii], 1981 June 3-1987 October 5; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 45, Folder 7)
    - [Rybinsk City Manifesto Author Unknown] 1980 August, Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 45, Folder 8)
    - [Sablin, Valerii], 1991 July 14-1992 November 18; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 45, Folder 9)
    - [Sablina, Tamara], 2006 December 18; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 45, Folder 10)
    - [Sadunaite, Nijole], 1977 April 4-1985 August 16; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 45, Folder 11)
    - [Safonov, Vitalii], 1978 October 10-1979 October 15; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 45, Folder 12)
    - [Safronov, A.], 1978 November 20; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 45, Folder 13)
    - [Safronov, Aleksei], 1976 May; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 45, Folder 14)
    - [Saginov, Kh.S.], 1983 February 2; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 45, Folder 15)
    - [Sakalys, Vladas], 1980 August 5-1980 November 21; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 45, Folder 16)
    - Sakharov [Andrei] [1/5], 1974 April 4-2002 June 1; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 45, Folder 17)
    - Sakharov [Andrei] [2/5], 1972 July 31-1989 January 4; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 45, Folder 18)
    - Sakharov [Andrei] [3/5], 1980 January 28-1985 May 22; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 45, Folder 19)
    - Sakharov [Andrei] [4/5], 1971 June 25-1983 April 29; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 45, Folder 20)
    - Sakharov [Andrei] [5/5], 1970 February 4-1980 February 7; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 45, Folder 21)
    - [Andrei] Sakharov [Elena] Bonner [1/2], 1985 April 10-2000 November 28; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 46, Folder 1)
    - [Andrei] Sakharov [Elena] Bonner [2/2], 1981 January 22-1985 March 17; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 46, Folder 2)
    - [Andrei] Sakharov [Elena] Bonner [1/2], 1979 April 25-1980 December 24; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 46, Folder 3)
    - [Andrei] Sakharov [Elena] Bonner [2/2], 1973 May 8-1979 April 18; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 46, Folder 4)
    - [Andrei] Sakharov w[ith] others, 1977 October 4-1989 October 12; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 46, Folder 5)
    - [Andrei] Sakharov with Others, 1973 June 25-1976 June 30; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 46, Folder 6)
    - [Sakhatov, Mamed], 1990 April 6-1990 April 13; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 46, Folder 7)
    - [Salum, Vello], 1981 July 14; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 46, Folder 8)
    - [Samkharadze, Begliar], 1945 December 20-1975 October; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 46, Folder 9)
    - [Samkharadze, Nikolai], 1974 September 12-1983 January 20; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 46, Folder 10)
    - [Samokhin, Andrei], 1975 October 15; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 46, Folder 11)
    - [Samsonova, Tamara], 1979 February 7; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 47, Folder 1)
    - [Saneliak, Stepan], 1976 May-1982 September; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 47, Folder 2)
    - [Sannikova, Elena], 1982 December 14-1983 February 25; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 47, Folder 3)
    - [Sapeliak, Stepan], 1976 July-1976 August; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 47, Folder 4)
    - [Sarbayova, Larissa], undated; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 47, Folder 5)
    - [Sartakov, P.K.], undated; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 47, Folder 6)
    - [Sashenkov, Andrei], 1991 March 2; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 47, Folder 7)
    - [Sasnauskas, Iulius], 1978 April 27-1979 December 16; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 47, Folder 8)
    - [Schastlivaia, Liliia], 1977 October 21; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 47, Folder 9)
    - [Schneider, Viktor], 1973 January 26-1973 July 26; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 47, Folder 10)
    - [Schwaderer, Emanuel], undated; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 47, Folder 11)
    - [Sedletsky, Viktor], 1979 September 22-1979 October 22; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 47, Folder 12)
    - [Seitmuratova, Aisha], 1977 October 4-1981 February 12; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 47, Folder 13)
    - [Selimov, A.], 1975 September 14-1976 January 23; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 47, Folder 14)
    - [Seliunin, Vasilii], 1990 February; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 47, Folder 15)
    - [Semanov, Sergei], 1982 September 26; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 47, Folder 16)
    - [Semeniuk, Klim], 1981 May-1985 February 4; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 47, Folder 17)
    - [Senderov, Valerii], 1981-1990 August 12; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 47, Folder 18)
    - [Serafina], undated; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 47, Folder 19)
    - Serebrov [Feliks], 1977 October 2-1982 January 27; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 47, Folder 20)
    - [Sereda, Mikhail], 1984 March 13-1984 May 21; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 47, Folder 21)
    - [Sergeev, Lev], 1970-1980 April 26; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 47, Folder 22)
    - [Sergienko, Aleksandr], 1974 April 16-1979 December 11; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 47, Folder 23)
    - [Serman, Ilya Zakharovich], undated; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 47, Folder 24)
    - [Seryi, Leonid], 1977 May-1984 October 8; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 47, Folder 25)
    - [Sevruk, Vatslav], 1971 March; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 47, Folder 26)
    - [Shaab, Iogannes], 1981-1982 August 27; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 47, Folder 27)
    - [Shabatura, Stefaniia], 1976 October 30; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 47, Folder 28)
    - [Shaebits, Adol'f], 1985 May 4; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 47, Folder 29)
    - [Shafarevich, Igor'], 1974 November 14; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 47, Folder 30)
    - [Shairian, Eduard], 1977; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 47, Folder 31)
    - [Shakalis, Vladas], 1981 January 1; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 47, Folder 32)
    - [Shakhberdian, Bagrat], 1975 September; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 47, Folder 33)
    - [Shakhnazarian, Bagrat], 1976; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 47, Folder 34)
    - [Shakhnazarian, Zaven], 1980 June 25; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 47, Folder 35)
    - [Shalamov, Varlam], 1982 January 20-1984 January 24; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 47, Folder 36)
    - [Shamanuri, Nazi], 1985 July 26-1987 October 23; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 47, Folder 37)
    - [Sharaev, Iu.], 1989 August; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 47, Folder 38)
    - [Sharygin, Nikolai], 1977 April 24-1978 November 20; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 47, Folder 39)
    - [Shatalov, Nikolai], 1978 May 30-1978 August 10; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 47, Folder 40)
    - [Shatalova, Tatiana], 1982 September 27; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 47, Folder 41)
    - [Shatravka, Aleksandr], 1982 January 18-1986 March 31; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 47, Folder 42)
    - Shatravka [Alexander], 1975 December 26-1986 August 10; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 47, Folder 43)
    - [Shatrov, Mikhail], 1987 December 14; Series 4 Subseries 4 (Box 48, Folder 1)